Dad!
(Dr Koothrappali:)Sorry.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I'm sure you won't grow
to hate each other.
(ringtone playing)
(Raj(on phone):)Hey, Leonard. What's up?
(Raj(on phone):)What? How did that happen?
(Raj(on phone):)Yeah, okay.
(Raj(on phone):)I'll be there as soon as I can.
(Raj(on phone):)Sorry. I have to run
to the university.
(Amy:)What's going on?
(Raj:)There's been a problem
with our experiment.
(Raj:)A bird got into the clean room.
(Dr Koothrappali:)You want me
to come?
Uh, no.
(Raj:)You had a long flight.
You stay here and relax.
"Relax."
Easy for you to say.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Your mother isn't cleaning out
your bank account.
40 years,
the woman never cleaned a thing.
(quietly): You're just
gonna leave him here?
"Relax," he says.
Yup. Bye.
(singing along to music):
♪ Here comes Santa Claus,
here comes Santa Claus ♪
♪ Right down Santa Claus Lane ♪
♪ Vixen and Blitzen
and all his reindeer ♪
♪ Pulling on
the reins... ♪
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I appreciate the ride...
♪ Bells are ringing,
children singing ♪
♪ All is merry
and bright ♪